# **Shirronda Caldwell**

# Housekeeping Supervisor - Shipley Manor

Wilmington, DE - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Shirronda-Caldwell/410328a78c0122c3

Experienced housekeeping supervisor possessing the ability to successfully lead an environmental service team to service excellence.

Possess skills to re-establish a work team to reach short and long term goals that gears team members to comply with company policy and standards.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Housekeeping Supervisor**

Shipley Manor - Wilmington, DE - March 2008 to Present

Currently supervise a total of twelve housekeeping staff members, develope master schedules, manage attendance calendars, delegate duties among staff members when fully and short staffed, control supplies, order monthly supplies, interview, hire, and train new housekeeping staff, coordinate and perform annual thorough cleaning of apartments and resident rooms, conduct monthly staff meetings and in-services, manage one of the company's credit cards, serve on the safety committee, and perform any other duties delegated by the director of the environmental services

Earned employee of the month during first two months of employment

Housekeeping department has been recognized by the company with an award for excellent service Successfully met state requirements at on-hundred percent during state inspection with zero deficiencies Possess the ability to work/function in stressful work situations

#### Personal Housekeeper/Self-Employed

Shirronda's TLC Cleaning & Healthcare Services - Wilmington, DE - 2006 to 2010

Provided commercial and residential cleaning services to customers

- Dusted furniture
- Wet wiped surfaces
- Shampooed carpets
- Vacuumed carpets
- Cleaned restrooms
- Swept and wet mopped floors
- Emptied trash receptacles
- Performed any other related tasks at the customer's request

## Housekeeper

Ellicott City Health & Rehabilitation Center - Ellicott City, MD - 2007 to 2008

Conducted general cleaning of common areas, resident's rooms, offices, emptied trash receptacles, vacuumed rooms and offices, swept and wet mopped bathroom floors, dusted in common areas, offices and resident's rooms, maintained cleanliness of the resident's rooms and all assigned areas and replenished paper and soap products

#### Custodian

Russell Toyota - Baltimore, MD - 2007 to 2008

Supervised three custodians ensuring the facility was cleaned in a professional manner, responsible for vacuuming offices, emptying trash receptacles, wet wiping desk tops, cleaning restrooms, sweeping and wet mopping floors

- Responsible for ensuring time cards were turned in before deadlines
- Communicated with head supervisor via telephone to report cleaning equipment malfunctions, problems or concerns during the shift, and need for supplies
- Locked the facility at the end of the shift after all staff had vacated the premises

## **EDUCATION**

# **Diploma in Surgical Technology**

Harrison Career Institute 2001 to 2002

## **Diploma in General Studies**

Christiana High School 1996 to 1999

# **Currently studing for diploma in Business Mangement**

Stratford Career Institute 2003

**SKILLS** 

Basic knowledge of Microsoft Word, Excel & Powerpoint